JACK WITBROCK FINLAY

ADDRESS: 3/12 Clare Place, Mt Wellington, Auckland, New Zealand

EMAIL: jack@jackfinlay.com PHONE: +64 22 603 5912

WEB: jackfinlay.com

GITHUB: github.com/JackWFinlay

Summary

Aspiring to build a successful career in Software Engineering. Constantly seeking to further skills and education through independent study.

Technical Skills

Skill	Experience	Where used
C#	2 years	University, Work, Self study
Java	2 years	University, Work
JavaScript	2 years	University, Work, Self Study
HTML/CSS	3 years	University, Work, Self study
SQL	2 years	University, Work
Version Control (Git, VSTS/TFS)	3 years	University, Work, Self study
ASP.NET MVC	2 Years	Work, Self study
Databases (MS SQL Server, MySQL, Oracle)	2 Years	University, Work, Self Study
Agile Methodologies	3 Years	University, Work

Education

Auckland University of Technology, Auckland, New Zealand

2013 - July 2016

■ Bachelor of Computer and Information Science - Software Development Major.

Experience

Analyst Programmer August 2016 - Present Gentrack Itd, Auckland ■ BASIC Analysis Debugging □ SQL Working with clients to fix defects and extend functions of utilities billing software. Role includes both analysis of codebase to determine cause of issues, and programming to fix issues and extend functionality. **April 2015 - August 2016 Technical Consultant Business Mechanix Itd, Auckland** □ C# □ HTML/CSS/Javascript ☐ ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework ■ SPARQL Web API Developed a website for international students to find study options in New Zealand. This role also involved managing and mentoring a team of three interns working over the 2015/16 summer. Secondary roles involved setup and management of Azure virtual machines, maintenance of C# applications, and ad-hoc customer support. **Intern Developer** December 2014 - February 2015 University of Auckland IT Services, Auckland □ Java □ Scriptella □ Bash

Intern developer role at IT Services. Worked on current and new projects. Reverse engineered an HTTP driver for Scriptella from the source code. Wrote various ad-hoc

References

References available on request

Scriptella, Groovy and Bash scripts.